(knocking)
Amy.
Amy?
(Amy:)That's Sheldon.
You're kidding!
How's my hair?
Sheldon, this-this isn't
a good time.
(Sheldon:)I don't care.
(Sheldon:)Amy, there was a song I
couldn't get out of my head.
(Sheldon:)Eventually, I realized
the song was about you,
(Sheldon:)and like that earworm, I can't
get you out of my heart.
(Sheldon:)So, what I'm trying to say is,
(Sheldon:)you're my heartworm.
The metaphorical kind, not-not
the poodle-killing kind.
W-W-W-What?
(Dave:)If I may...
(Dave:)I believe
what he's saying,
(Dave:)in a charming
and delightful way,
(Dave:)is that he loves you
and wants you back.
(Dave:)Dave Gibbs,
huge fan of your work.
(Dave:)Oh.
Don't mind me.
I'm-I'm sorry; I didn't
realize you were on a date.
No, it-it... it's okay.
Keep going?